autopilot101.com 2015-12-29

# 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

We use information you provide about yourself or others to complete transactions for which such information is provided. Such transactions may include administering services, filling orders, supplying requested information (e.g., via email, download, or subscription-based services), advertising new products and services, and contacting you. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, disclaimers, and terms & conditions, we do not share this information with outside parties without your permission. 

Occasionally, we also use information you provide about yourself or others to inform you of new and/or improved services as well as to conduct member surveys to improve our services. Lifestyle Publishing reserves the right to published quotes, names, photos, and any other information you provide as a voluntary testimonial regarding our products or services.

We may use personally identifiable information to provide targeted content and commerce opportunities to you based on demographic, behavioral, and/or areas-of-interest information.

We offer products and services created by Lifestyle Publishing and other 3rd-party suppliers for sale and for free to our customers. In some cases, we may use cookies, tracking technology, and similar tools to determine the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing methods and to ensure we get commissions due when selling third-party products and services. You may turn off cookies by following guidelines provided in the Help section of your Internet browser(s).

We never use, share, sell or otherwise distribute any personally identifiable information or email addresses provided to us online in ways or for reasons except as related to the usage presented above.

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>  Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google�s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Lifestyle Publishing has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

Collection of Personal Information

When visiting Lifestyle Publishing and other sites owned by Lifestyle Publishing, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.  
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Lifestyle Publishing then you may contact us at [rbstoker@comcast.net](mailto:rbstoker@comcast.net)
